localbizbuilders.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Local Marketing Source

We at Local Marketing Source, LLC and our affiliated companies are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information you share with us.  We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security.  We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

Any information you may disclose in any public areas of our web sites become public information.  Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.

You must be eighteen (18) years or older to access this web site.  Any person under eighteen years of age is not permitted to access this web site for any reason.  It is our policy to comply with all applicable laws related to children’s privacy.  No information obtained by this web site falls within the Child Online Privacy Act (COPA) due to the age restrictions for use and is not monitored as doing so.

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server may automatically recognize the consumer’s domain name and e-mail address (where possible). We may collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number, fax number, and payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address).

The information we collect may be used for internal review, used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, and used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes.

With respect to cookies: We may use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, and customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we may have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.  We do not control use of these cookies and other data gathering practices and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by writing to us at the above address.  Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from future postal mailings.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by writing to us at the above address. Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from future outbound calls.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes. Your use of this site after such changes are implemented constitutes your acknowledgment and acceptance of these changes.  Please consult this privacy statement prior to every use for any changes.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to a description of information that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by sending a written request to the address listed below.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to the site.  Consumers can have this information corrected by sending a written request to the address listed below.

With respect to security: We have security measures in place to protect the information under our control.  While we make every effort to ensure the security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers” from illegally obtaining this information.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us via email at  [support@localmarketingsource.com](mailto:support@localmarketingsource.com)This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it .

Copyright © Local Marketing Source, LLC, 70 Val Vista Dr. #181, Gilbert, AZ 85296
